[
  {
    "front": ".hide()",
    "back": "Hide Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".show()",
    "back": "Show Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".hide()",
    "back": "Hide Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".show()",
    "back": "Show Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".hide()",
    "back": "Hide Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".show()",
    "back": "Show Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".hide()",
    "back": "Hide Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".show()",
    "back": "Show Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".hide()",
    "back": "Hide Element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".show()",
    "back": "Show Element."
  }  
]